MICHAŁ BIENIEK

FULL STACK DEVELOPER





CODECOOL

Contact

michalbieniek02@gmail.com

+48789113371

www.linkedin.com/in/

michalbieniek02

github.com/michalbieniek02

Self Definition

I am open minded, I like resolving problems that I encounter, I like teamwork and I find myself comfortable around people. I am passionate about the world of programming and I love to learn new things

Strength

I am experienced in React and C#, with a proficiency in working with various APIs. My skills include problem-solving, effective communication with both technical and nontechnical side, and collaborative work within a team. I have a strong aptitude for learning new technologies, taking on challenges, and I am truly passionate about being a programmer

Mentor Opinion

"Michał is skillfull job ready student, eager to learn and grow. During our cooperation he managed to deliver on time and write high quality code."

— Dominik Starzyk, mentor



Hard Skills























Recent Projects

CHECKEDAPP

https://github.com/CheckedAppTeam/CheckedApp

Application that can help you organise your bag when you are traveling and also find items needed when traveling to various places. Its a group project with 3 contributors

MY PORTFOLIO

https://github.com/michalbieniek02/PortfolioSite

Its my portfolio which i did using react, and i experimented with next and tailwind (project in progress)

PARTY GAME

https://github.com/michalbieniek02/PartyGame

This is game that is able to connect people into group by and randomize one of them to have different question and then comparing it

Work Experience

Warsaw stadium cleaner (2020 - 2020) — Impel Cleaning Production line worker (2021 - 2021) — International Plastik Polska, Mińsk Mazowiecki Waiter (2021 - 2021) — Cuda na kiju Multitap Bar, Warszawa

Education

junior fullstack developer (2023 - 2024) — Codecool none (2022 - 2023) — Polish-Japanese Academy of Information Technology high school education (2019 - 2021) — Military class in high school (Math, Physics)

Spoken Languages

Polish — Native **English** — Advanced **Russian** — Basic **German** — Basic Spanish — Basic

